[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Senator, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, I'm doing great, Piers, thank you so much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Were you harboring any inspirations to be the last- minute VP?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "No, no harboring of any aspirations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul"]}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "So you two couldn't be further apart, really, could you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "CD", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, you know, I have a lot of respect for Paul.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "How are you going to ensure as a party that your message wins the day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Well, the interesting thing here is the facts actually are on our side when it comes to, you know, making the pitch to the American people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "If tax cuts are the answer, why did we end up after eight years of George Bush with the financial crisis we ended up with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Well, the financial crisis really wasn't related to the tax cuts.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Is it actually going to work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Well, there's a lot of evidence to it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "What was the rate on the date he left?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Well, no, because we had a financial meltdown.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "But -- to be -- but to be fair, you can't quote 4 percent when his final percentage was what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "TO", "VB", ":", "CC", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, no, I understand that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["4 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "Yes, but what was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "The linkage -- I don't -- I don't remember.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "What did you make of what Senator Santorum was tub thumping away there with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Well, I agree with that first thing he said about, hello and thank you for having me on the show.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Santorum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Anything else ?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "That is the Democrat view, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "I think it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "The Democrats must be a little bit worried, aren't they, that this bandwagon currently rolling, the Romney/Ryan bandwagon, could resonate to a victory in November?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Who found the body?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Two uniforms and a set of car bombs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Manhattan"]}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Yes, you got prints?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Looks like half of Manhattan handed this door.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "You ever think your friends who place with valet parking and accused you of some stranger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Or is the purpose of the book to put out enough doubt to make people just question, again, the veracity of what they've been told?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "That's a very good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "And if so, by who and why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "WP", "CC", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Well, the scientific evidence is overwhelming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "What is your theory about who may have killed her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Well, it wasn't the Kennedys, which is, you know, some people would think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "So what do you believe happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Well, I know what happened, and so do you and it's all in the public domain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Because you're grouping that with this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "And if I said we didn't, would you summarily dismiss everything I said before that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "And about being brilliant, yes, why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Welcome, P.J. How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Hi, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["P.J."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["P.J."]}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Hi, P.J.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Before we go on to politics, are you a -- are you a natural conspiracy theorists yourself, P.J.?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "No, I'm not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["P.J."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "On your show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "With you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Which Democrat brought this country to its knees?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "P.J., over to you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Hope, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I'm doing great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "As a British man, do you appreciate goal keeping?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "When you made the save, what goes through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Well, let's talk about before I made the save.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VB", "POS", "VB", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Why is that, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "We've come a long way, let's be honest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "It's also not unhelpful that you radiate beauty yourself, is it, Hope?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "Yeah, you know what, that's not true though.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "What was the most important thing that you wanted to get out there about that whole time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "OLO: It's not really the most important thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "You think I'm being hard on myself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "I think you're slightly overdoing the whole bad wrap thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]